

KSENIIA ZHYKINA

PROJECT
MANAGER /
DELIVERY
MANAGER

CONTACT DETAILS

Address: Wroclaw Phone: +48 575 110 858 E-mail: zhykinak@gmail.com

SUMMARY

12 years' experience in media industry. Hands on media planning processes and building strategies for promoting goods and services using TV and digital advertising.

6 years' experience in management and planning activities of a team, motivation of team members and team performance to achieve organizational goals and improve the quality and volume of ongoing commercial deals.

WORK HISTORY

General Manager

Cotrestone Group (6.2021-2.2022)

- Recruitment and organization of new departments connected with closing and realization of commercial contracts (sales team, strategic marketing and media planning department, creative and video production team)
- Developing sales strategy and tactics driving business in key market segments and accounts
- Developing and manage key relationships with clients at TOP management organizational level
- Running business negotiations, processing contracts, closing deals with clients and key partners (TV, digital platforms for advertising campaigns)
- Using analysis and econometric modeling to achieve positive ROI for media investments (TV and digital media campaigns)
- Accelerate the growth of revenue for the business and building the customer's and project's pipeline

Sales Director B2B

StarLight Media (2.2016-3.2021)

- Analysis of variable Ukrainian market categories, understanding of world markets main features and local customers' characteristics
- Building strong trust relationships with existing and new clients
- Running negotiation process to achieve win-win agreements with clients
- Carrying out a major media investment analysis and preparation of a media strategy for clients (short- and longterm)
- Cooperating with other team members and business units during creation and implementation of media strategies (TV direct advertising, TV sponsorship)
- Cooperation with production and creative teams to achieve high quality brands integration into channel's projects, top TV shows and series of the StarLight Media Group
- Monitoring TV advertising campaigns performance with respect to core KPIs (TRP, GRP, Aff, Reach, CPP, COV) according to Nielsen data and analytics

New Business Manager

TRK Lux (11.2014-1.2016)

- Planning and implementation strategies to attract customers for media services (TV, radio, digital)
- Creation of new GRP pricing strategy for radio advertising campaign using GFK metrics and analytics
- Negotiations with other media holdings to form a single comprehensive offer for advertisers
- Preparing presentations and offers for potential Clients
- Market analyzing and developing the training courses for the sales team to create more competitive offers



KSENIIA ZHYKINA

MARKETING MANAGER/EXPERT

CONTACT DETAILS

Address: Wroclaw Phone: +48 575 110 858 E-mail: zhykinak@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Perfect analytical and problemsolving skills. Excellent negotiation and communication skills.
- Great organizational, collaboration and communication skills.
- Presentation skills; presence and credibility in front of key stakeholders.
- Ability to translate business requirements into technology solutions
- Ability to translate visions into executable projects with clarity and purpose.
- Hands on experience in demonstrating thought leadership, sales leadership and delivery leadership.
- Proven experience in creating efficient offers.
- Strategic thinking.
- Ability to work with big data structuring, identifying trends and patterns, making conclusions.
- Proficient in Microsoft Office.

Sales Manager

Ukrainian Media Holding (8.2010-10.2014)

- Radio advertising market analysis
- Creating effective media strategies for radio advertising based on GfK and TNS data and analytics
- Assisting with challenging client requests
- Experienced on using CRM software (Zoho CRM)
- Created wide base of regular customers (FMCG, pharmaceutical, gas stations, etc)

EDUCATION

Ukrainian State University of Finance and International Trade

Master's Degree in International Economy

LANGUAGE

English – C1 Russian and Ukrainian – native speaker